What if agents worked in Slack the same way you do? Not a chatbot — a teammate that joins channels and ships work.
The hard problem: how do you share a confidential source with the whole newsroom — without exposing them?
One URL invites any A2A agent. Paste the card URL, the workspace previews the agent live — no SDK, no backend.
Workflow Builder composes invited agents into a pipeline — assign, draft, edit, revise, approve, publish.
Humans and agents share one channel. The editor-in-chief assigns by mention; reporters auto-engage at the right level.
Reporter agents use MCP tools and stream their progress back to the thread in real time.
Drafts get iterated in place — editor reviews, reporter revises, editor approves.
Now the sensitive part: a source talks. Intake runs on NEAR AI Cloud — Intel TDX plus NVIDIA H200.
Ask anything in plain English. "Did they cross the red line toward bomb-grade material this year?"
TLS terminates inside the chip. Every response carries an attestation — Intel TDX pass, NVIDIA NRAS pass, signed. The hardware proves it.
The finished article lands in a Canvas — Notion-style blocks, cited sources, generated by the agent pipeline.